Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.D: Co-operatives, 1921-2009; 3.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 oversize flat box
    - Cooperative Builder: Cooperative Publishing Association, Superior, WI, 1947, 1949, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Co-op News: Co-operative Union, Inc., Chicago, IL, 1943, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Producer: Journal of Co-operative Business: Co-operative Wholesale Society Ltd., Manchester, England, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Wheatsheaf: Co-operative Wholesale Society Ltd., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Cooperator: Eastern Cooperative League, New York, NY, 1936, 1947-1955 (Box 4, Folder 31-37)
    - ECL Leadership Bulletin: Eastern Cooperative League, 1942 (Box 162, Folder 27)
    - Benefits Review: Laborers-Employers Cooperation & Education Trust, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Co-op Cornucopia: Madison Development Corp., Madison, WI, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Central Co-Operative Wholesale Year Book: Mast Printing, Co., Superior, WI, 1934 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Co-op Highlights: Mid-Eastern Cooperatives, Inc., Carlstadt, NJ, 1957-1968, 1970-1971, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 39-42, Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Co-op Clubs: Midland Cooperative Wholesale, Educational Department, Minneapolis, MN, circa 1950s (Box 162, Folder 18)
    - Program Guide: Midland Cooperative Wholesale, Minneapolis, MN, circa 1950s (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Co-operative Official: National Co-operative Managers' Association Ltd./Co-operative Secretaries' Association/National Union of Co-operative Officials, Manchester, England, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Provender: Northwest Provender Alliance, Seattle, WA, 1979-1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Co-op Bulletin: Peninsula Cooperative Association, Inc., Hampton, VA, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Plainfield Co-op Newsletter: Plainfield Co-op, Plainfield, VT, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - PCC Sound Consumer: Puget Consumers' Co-op, Seattle, WA, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Southern States Patron Annual Report Issue: Southern States Cooperative, Richmond, VA, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Cooperative League Cooperator: The Eastern States Cooperative League, New York, NY, 1938-1946 (Box 23, Folder 8-13)
  - Subseries I.E: Education Workers, 1933-2002; 14.25 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 10 oversize flat boxes
    Encompassing both private and public educators, this series collects serials issued by unions and federations of teachers, clerical staff, college educators, and retired educators. Many serials are issued by federal- and state-level coalitions (American Federation of Teachers; National Education Association; New York State Teachers Association), often containing information on contract negotiations, regulations governing employment and tenure, and advocacy in the field.
    - Journal of Teacher Education: American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - The Rise of Organized Labor - Worker Security and Employer Rights: American Education Publications, Middletown, CT, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - AFT Action/AFT In Action: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1971-1972, 1977-1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - AFT News Clips: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - American Federation of Teachers Monthly Bulletin: American Federation of Teachers, Chicago, IL, 1924-1926 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - American Federation of Teachers Semi-Monthly Bulletin: American Federation of Teachers, Chicago, IL, 1921-1926 (Box 28, Folder 2, Box 38, Folder 1)
    - lifeTIMES: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1988, 1989, 1991, 1993, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - On Campus: American Federation of Teachers, 1985-1994 (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
    - Reports of Vice Presidents to the American Federation of Teachers June 1948 Thru June 1949: American Federation of Teachers, 1948-1949 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Tenure Under Attack: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Washington Newsletter: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1942-1967 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Update: American Federation of Teachers - Department of Organization/FNHP Division, Washington, DC, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia Teacher: American Federation of Teachers - Local 192, Philadelphia, PA, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Labor Education News: American Federation of Teachers (AFL-CIO) - Local 189, Park Forest, IL, 1967, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Ninth Annual Midwest Workers' Education Program: American Labor Education Service, Milwaukee, WI, 1948 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Report of the Director: American Labor Education Service, New York, NY, 1943 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Foresight: Black Teachers Workshop, Detroit, MI, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Boston Union Teacher: Boston Teachers Union - American Federation of Teachers Local 66, Boston, MA, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - California AFT Teacher: California Federation of Teachers (AFT, AFL-CIO), Oakland, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Labor in the Schools: California Federation of Teachers (AFT, AFL-CIO), Oakland, CA, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Planning Work: California Newsreel, San Francisco, CA, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - CLEAR Newsletter: Center for Labor Education and Research, University of Hawaii, Honolulu, HI, 1988, 1994. 1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Union Teacher: Chicago Teachers Union, Local 1-AFT, AFL-CIO, Chicago, IL, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Critique: Cleveland Teachers Union, Cleveland, OH, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Coalition of New York Schoolworkers Newsletter: Coalition of New York Schoolworkers, New York, NY, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - New York City Schoolworker: Coalition of New York Schoolworkers, New York, NY, 1978, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Colorado Teacher: Colorado Federation of Teachers, Denver, CO, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - CSA Contract Update: Council of Supervisors and Administrators - Local 1 - American Federation of School Administrators (AFL-CIO) (NYS Federation of School Administrators), Brooklyn, NY, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - CSA Newsletter: Council of Supervisory Associates, Brooklyn, NY, 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Just for the Health of It!: Day Care Council - Local 205, DC 1707 Welfare Fund, New York, NY, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Detroit Teacher: Detroit Federation of Teachers, Detroit, MI, 1954, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 6, Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Dunbar Craftsman: Dunbar Trade School, Chicago, IL, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - College Teacher: Empire State Federation of Teachers (AFT), Hicksville, NY, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Empire State Teacher: Empire State Federation of Teachers (AFT), New York, NY, 1957-1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Heritage: Heritage Publishing Co., Los Angeles, CA, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Hudson A.M. Shore/Hudson Shore Labor School Newsletter: Hudson Shore Labor School, West Park, NY, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - New Rank and Filer: Independent Workers Coordinating Committee, Detroit, MI, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - IAM Education Bulletin: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers - Education Department, Washington, DC, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Workers' Education - Bulletin of the International Federation of Workers' Education Associations: International Federation of Workers' Education Associations, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Bulletin: Joint Committee of Teachers' Organization, New York, NY, 1934, 1940, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 11, Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Labor: Labor Cooperative Educational & Publishing Society, Washington, DC, 1986-1989 (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
    - Labor Educator Monthly Report: Labor Educator, New York, NY, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Long Island Union Teacher: Long Island American Federation of Teachers Council, Farmingdale, NY, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7361)
    - MVT\UFT Newsletter: Manhattan Vocational-Technical High School (UFT), New York, NY, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Reporter: Education Committee News: Massachusetts Federation of Labor, Boston, MA, 1949-1952 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Michigan Teacher: Michigan Federation of Teachers (AFT, AFL-CIO), Detroit, MI, 1946, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Briefing Memo: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Communicator: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Daily Journal: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - DuShane Fund Reports: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - NEA News: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - NEA Reporter: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - NEA Research Memo: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Washington Memo on Federal Education Programs: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - What's Happening Today: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - New Jersey Teachers: New Jersey State Federation of Teachers, Newark, NJ, 1945, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - College Newsletter: New York College Teachers Union - Local 537, New York, NY, 1938-1942 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - NYEA Advocate: New York Educators Association, Albany, NY, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - NYSTA Research: 1971-72 Teachers Salary Schedules and Selected Agreement Provisions: New York State Teachers Association - Research Division, Albany, NY (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - 1972 Delegate Handbook: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Challenger: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Constitution and Bylaws: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - EO News: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1970 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Guide Lines for Local Leaders: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Legislative Bulletin: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - NYSTA News Trends: New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA), Albany, NY, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Active NYSUT Retiree: New York State United Teachers - Editorial Board of the Retirees Organizing Committee, Albany, NY, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Legislative Memorandum: New York State United Teachers (AFT, AFL-CIO/NYS AFL-CIO), Albany, NY, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Benefits Newsletter: New York University, New York, NY, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - NTU Bulletin: Newark Teachers Union - Local 481 (AFT, AFL-CIO), Newark, NJ, 1965, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Red Pencil: Radical Teachers Group, Boston, MA, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - SCTA Speak Out: Sachem Central Teacher's Association, Lake Ronkokoma, NY, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - ILR Alumni Bulletin: School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Ithaca, NY, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Seattle Labor School News: Seattle Labor School, Seattle, WA, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Teachers' Cause: Teachers' Cause, Alexandria, VA, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Why did they fire my teacher?: Teachers Defense Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Hey Teach!: Teachers for a Democratic Society, New York, N.Y., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Education for Democracy - Annual Educational Conference: Teachers Union - Local 5, New York, NY, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Washington, D.C. Teacher: Teachers Union - Local 6 (AFT, AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Schools and the fight for peace and freedom - Teachers Union Annual Yearbook: Teachers Union of New York, Local 555, circa 1940s (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - College Newsletter: Teachers Union of New York, Local 555 (UPW, CIO) - College Chapter, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Pension Primer: Teachers Union of the City of New York, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Teaching for Change: Teaching for Change, Washington, DC, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Labor Education News: UCLA Center for Labor Research & Education, Los Angeles, CA, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Bulletin: Union of Private School Teachers, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - City University UFCCT Reporter: United Federation of College Teachers, New York, NY, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - UFCT University Reporter: United Federation of College Teachers, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - ATSS/UFT Journal: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Community College UFT Reporter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Contract Update/Contract Bulletin: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1996, 2000, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Insider: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Last Week at The UFT: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - UFT Bulletin: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1990-1992 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - UFT Political Action Reporter: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - UFT Professional Bulletin Board: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - UFT Relay: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - UFT Update: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - United Teacher: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1960-1971 (Box 33, Folder 1-7, Box 34, Folder 1-5, Box 35, Folder 1-10, Box 36, Box 37, Box 1-4, Box 38, Folder 9)
    - United Teacher Magazine: United Federation of Teachers, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Delegate Assembly - minutes: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1987-1991 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Issues in Education: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - UFT United Action: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - United Teacher (New York City Edition): United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
    - Where We Stand: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - UFT Chapter Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2, American Federation of Teachers (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1977-1982, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Damrosch Digest: United Federation of Teachers - Local 2, American Federation of Teachers (AFL-CIO) - Junior High School 136, Bx. Chapter, Bronx, NY, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - New Coalition: United Federation of Teachers - New Coalition Caucus, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Page: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Membership Meeting - minutes: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1987-1990 (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - RTC/UFT Monthly Newsletter: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - RTC-UFT Retiree: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1987-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - RTC-UFT Update: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, New York, NY, 1988, 1990, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Committee: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - UFT Retired Action: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter, Local 2 (AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Si Beagle Learning Centers Program: United Federation of Teachers - Retired Teachers' Chapter/Welfare Fund, New York, NY, 1989-1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Special EDition: United Federation of Teachers - Teacher Center Professional Development Program, New York, NY, 1987, 1991-1994, 1997, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
    - Retiree Advocate: United Federation of Teachers - Teachers Action Caucus, Member of the New Action Coalition, Brooklyn, NY, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Pension News: United Federation of Teachers Pension Committee, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - News From the War Zone - Staley Workers' Solidarity Report: United Paperworkers International Union/Allied Industrial Workers of America (UPIU/AIW) - Local 7837 - War Zone Education Foundation, Decatur, IL, 1993-1996, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Laurel Williams' Layoff Must Be Prevented mobilization leaflet: United Staff Association of NYU Local 3882 (NYSUT, AFT, AFL-CIO), New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - United Teacher (New York State Edition): United Teachers of New York State/AFT (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Unity Committee Election News: Unity Committee, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Labor Education Newsletter: Virginia Polytechnic Institute College of Business, Blacksburg, VA, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Reuther Library Newsletter: Walter P. Reuther Library, Detroit, MI, 1991, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Report of the Executive Committee: Workers Education Bureau of America, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Workers Education in the United States 1929-1933: Workers Education Bureau of America, New York, NY (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Workers Education Center Bulletin: Workers Education Center, New York, NY, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - 189 News: Workers' Education Local 189, Detroit, MI, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Newsletter: Workers' Education Local 189, Lynn, MA, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Union News: Workers' Education Local 189, New York, NY, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Winter Conference: Workers' Education Local 189, Washington, DC, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Subseries I.F: Entertainment, 1937-1999; 4 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 2 oversize boxes
    This series collects serials, bulletins, and newsletters issued by unions representing workers in the entertainment industry, including several publications issued by the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists; the International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees; and by local chapters of the National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians.
    - AFTRA/Thoughts: AFTRA-Twin Cities Local, Minneapolis, MN, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - AFRA File: American Federation of Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Stand By!: American Federation of Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1975, 1977-1981 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - On the Air: American Federation of Radio Arts, New York, NY, 1948, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - AFTRA 1958-1960 National code of fair practice for recorder commercials for television broadcasting purposes: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - AFTRA's 30th Anniversary Ball ephemera: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 70)
    - Executive Secretary's Letter: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 162, Folder 20)
    - Your 1958 Convention: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, New York, NY (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Stand By!: American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - New York Local, New York, NY, 1951, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Official Journal of Local 802 A.F. of M.: Associated Musicians of Greater New York - Local 802 (AFM), 1932-1934 (Box 23, Folder 29, Box 38, Folder 13)
    - ACTRAScope: Association of Canadian Television and Radio Artists, Toronto, Canada, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Flash: Graphic Artists Guild, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - East Coast News Notes: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Eastern Region, Local 600, New York, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Call Sheet: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Locals 600 & 161, New York, NY, 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Call Sheet: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE) - Locals 644 & 161, New York, NY, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - IATSE Official Bulletin: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Moving Picture Technicians, Artists and Allied Crafts of the United States and Canada (IATSE) (AFL-CIO, CLC), New York, NY, 1989-1992, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Photographed...by: International Photographers of the Motion Picture Industry (IATSE) - Local 644, New York, NY, 1943-1946, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Art Works: Labor Heritage Foundation, Washington, DC, 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Labor Stage: Labor Stage, Inc., New York, NY, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Lab-Log: Motion Picture Laboratory Technician - Local 702 (IATSE), New York, NY, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Local 15 in Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NABET 15 in Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1982-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), Chicago, IL, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), New York, NY, 1978-1999 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - NABET Newsletter: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), Scarsdale, NY, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - In Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET) - Local 15, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - NABET 15 Highlights: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local 15, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Work Lines: Ontario Workers Arts and Heritage Center, Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Labor's Challenge: Photo-History Magazine, Concord, NH, 1937 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Screen Actor News Hollywood: Screen Actors Guild, Hollywood, CA, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - San Francisco Actor: Screen Actors Guild - San Francisco Branch, San Francisco, CA, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Sound Track: Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild - Local 109 (United Office and Professional Workers of America, CIO), New York, NY, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Screen Writer: Screen Writers Guild, Hollywood, CA, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Made in U.S.A.: WGBH Educational Foundation, Boston, MA, 1978-1984 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Musicians' Voice: New York, NY, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - People's Songs, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Subseries I.G: Farmworkers and Agricultural Unions, 1932-2002; 2.25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 oversize flat box